// questions.js
const multiquestions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Which of the following are programming languages?",
    options: ["HTML", "Python", "CSS", "JavaScript"],
    correctAnswers: ["Python", "JavaScript"] 
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which of these are JavaScript frameworks/libraries?",
    options: ["React", "Vue", "Django", "Angular"],
    correctAnswers: ["React", "Vue", "Angular"]
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which are fruits?",
    options: ["Apple", "Potato", "Mango", "Tomato"],
    correctAnswers: ["Apple", "Mango", "Tomato"]
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which of these are search engines?",
    options: ["Google", "Bing", "Firefox", "DuckDuckGo"],
    correctAnswers: ["Google", "Bing", "DuckDuckGo"]
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of the following are CSS frameworks?",
    options: ["Bootstrap", "TailwindCSS", "React", "Materialize"],
    correctAnswers: ["Bootstrap", "TailwindCSS", "Materialize"]
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which of these are planets?",
    options: ["Mars", "Sun", "Earth", "Moon"],
    correctAnswers: ["Mars", "Earth"]
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which of the following are mammals?",
    options: ["Dog", "Shark", "Bat", "Snake"],
    correctAnswers: ["Dog", "Bat"]
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which of these are NoSQL databases?",
    options: ["MongoDB", "MySQL", "Redis", "PostgreSQL"],
    correctAnswers: ["MongoDB", "Redis"]
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which of these are programming paradigms?",
    options: ["OOP", "Functional", "Agile", "Procedural"],
    correctAnswers: ["OOP", "Functional", "Procedural"]
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which are valid HTML tags?",
    options: ["<div>", "<html>", "<main>", "<bodyy>"],
    correctAnswers: ["<div>", "<html>", "<main>"]
  }
];

export default multiquestions;
